[radio host over radio] Turn it up.
Turn it up!
[man over radio] What's up, y'all?
This is Paulo Brown, voice of the favela.
Keeping the good vibes coming,
because every step you take
is a step closer to the dream.
And you're almost there.
["Forte Pra Dar Sorte"
by MC Hariel playing]
[brakes screeching]
[whirring]
[squeaking]
-[inaudible]
-[dogs barking]
[indistinct chatter]
[buzzing]
[whirring]
[flapping]
[revving]
[inaudible]
[whirring]
[meows]
[bird chirping]
[revving]
[song fades]
[woman] Yeah, that view
never gets old, does it?
-The only thing getting old is us.
-[woman chuckles]
If you knew what I go through
at that office…
Sometimes I don't even have time
to breathe.
[man] Imagine
when you get your own office.
-God willing! [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
Gimme a few years, I'll get there.
Baby steps though, huh?
How's the record label coming along?
Oh, I'm tryna live more purposeful
these days.
I have the church stuff,
and Chiquinho on the side.
-Kid's more than enough work. [chuckles]
-Adulting, huh?
Have you two been talking?
Eh, barely. Have you?
Nah, not really.
I hear more about him than from him.
Scheyla fills me in.
He hasn't seen the kids in a long time.
She says Nando's not himself these days.
I miss it being the three of us.
All together.
[pensive music playing]
Same here.
But he's out there.
On top of the world.
With more responsibilities
and more problems.
Where he's at, I doubt
he'll ever come back to Brazil.
["Balkanika" by Relativ playing]
[helicopter blades whirring]
BELGRADE - SERBIA
[in Serbian] Inbound for landing.
[man, in English] Ah, there he is!
Hey, brother.
-You good? Good to see you.
-Yeah, all good.
[song ends]
BALKAN HOTEL
[indistinct chatter]
[motorcycle revving]
Moicano.
Same deal, got me?
I got your back, ND.
[sirens wailing in distance]
[club bass pounding in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
["Hocu Sve" by Krtina
playing over speakers]
[indistinct chatter, cheering]
-[song continues in distance]
-[indistinct chatter]
Okay, wait here.
If things get loud, you come in.
ND, long time.
Sascha. Bojan.
-[exhales]
-[ND] This is Paulo.
Our partner from accounts.
So he take care of the numbers.
And you take care of us.
[ND] That's right.
Okay. Fill me in then.
We were just saying
that the last shipment you sent
was a success.
We make the Japanese, Chinese, Australian,
everybody happy.
And so this time we want double.
With same split.
Fifty percent before delivery,
fifty percent after delivery.
Divided between the crypto,
weapons, real estate, and soccer.
Which Brazilians love just as much as us.
The best deal's a finished deal.
And while we're at it, why don't we settle
the shortfall from the last shipment.
[chuckles] Shortfall?
[tense music playing]
Adding up
the money and the assets…
you're about two million short
from the last shipment.
[in Serbian] They say
we didn't pay in full.
[in English] All the transfers
and contributions was made.
The numbers don't lie, bro.
What are you saying?
My brother's a liar?
We're not here to cause problems, guys.
We're here to make a deal.
With interest.
Now you want us to make receipt
for taxes we owe you, man?
Or how about your word is my receipt, man?
[in Serbian] Maybe
you got the numbers wrong.
Or you lied to your brother.
[in English] Between you
and my own brother,
I trust my brother.
You should know, man.
Everyone's a brother in the favela.
But not here.
Here, brother is flesh.
First, we'll settle the shortfall
from the last time.
[inhales, exhales]
Then we can talk about the next shipment.
[in Serbian] They're blackmailing us.
They want more money,
or they'll stop selling.
But we do business with or without them.
[in English] All right, here's the deal.
You apologize to us.
And you make new delivery.
Or we will find a new partner.
Didn't you live with your uncle in Brazil?
Petar Ilic.
[laughs]
[ND] Nice name.
Three years.
Let me tell you something
that Petar clearly didn't.
Ninety five percent of the blow
that makes its way through Europe
I bring here.
Without us, you two have no business.
[dramatic sting]
You think you're back in Brazil, huh?
[club music playing]
[club music continues in distance]
[tense music playing]
-[gunshot]
-[Moicano grunts]
-[gunshots]
-[indistinct shouts]
[ND] Get down! Get down, fuck!
[gunshots stop]
[tense music continues]
-[screaming]
-[gunshots]
[gun clicks]
[Sasha grunts]
[suspenseful music playing]
[inhales, exhales]
[ND] Did you really think
you were gonna kill me?
I've been to the other side, man.
And I won't be going back.
Let's head out.
[indistinct chatter]
Do you know what you just did?
Who the fuck gave you the go-ahead
to do that?
They were trying to kill us, ND.
[intriguing music playing]
NANDO BETWEEN TWO WORLDS
- A SINTONIA FILM
[music fades]
-[woman] Happy Father's Day!
-[crowd cheering]
Hey!
Yeah! Enzo! [kiss]
["Se Essa Rua" by Mc Vitória playing]
[chuckles]
[boy] I had it at home.
Sorry?
I had it. I had it at home.
Ah. [chuckles]
Too bad I wasn't there
to see you prove it.
Hm. How's tonight?
No, I can't. I have a dinner thing
with my family later.
Hmm… You're celebrating Father's Day?
No, it's just dinner with my grandma.
We're the only ones
not celebrating the holiday, I guess. Hmm?
Yeah. But let's hang another time.
[boy] I don't know what's worse.
Having a dad that died or…
or one who disappeared, like mine.
[skateboard rolling away]
[pensive music playing]
[engine idling]
[ND] You know how it goes, man.
Those guys were already on us, you know?
So when the one guy pulled his gun,
Moicano drew his straight away, man.
And you know the rest, brother.
If you draw, you have to shoot,
no other way.
[man over phone] Fuck, bro.
These guys
have been our partners for years.
We need to fix this,
clean up this mess, ND.
[ND] I'm out of here, man.
Going straight to Bosnia.
After that, Italy.
Soon as I'm in a safe spot,
I'm gonna sort this out with them myself.
You're aware that Petar Ilic
isn't just the Serbians' boss, right?
He's also their uncle.
He'll want payback.
Brother,
I just wanted to ask you
to look out for my family.
Until I can prove
that those rats started this whole thing.
You're well aware that for the Serbians,
blood can only be paid for
with more blood.
Don't you worry, ND.
We'll step up our security.
As long as you're gone,
no one's gonna fuck
with your family, okay?
Hm.
[vibrating]
INCOMING VIDEO CALL
SCHEYLA
[ND] Okay.
I'm outta here, Joel.
We're in this together.
Thank you. Talk soon.
[woman] Enzo, talk to Daddy.
[game chiming]
Happy Father's Day.
[chuckles]
Thank you, my Enzo.
How did the performance go at school?
Good. Grandma and Mommy really liked it.
Kinda sucks you weren't there though.
But your papa was there in spirit
with you guys, okay?
Did your mom record it?
Tell her to send it to me.
I want to see it, okay?
How are things going over there, bud?
School, karate…
The same. Not much has changed.
[ND] The same?
That's it?
Your sister hasn't called
to wish me happy Father's Day.
Where is she?
She's outside with Grandma.
Grandma, do you really think
my mom would let me?
-No way.
-[chuckles]
[Grandma laughs]
-And neither will I, actually.
-[laughs]
Oh, it's bad enough
that your mother dated boys at school
without me knowing.
But I'm not like my mom.
And besides,
I have brought up Murilo a few times.
I know, honey.
But you're so young,
so much life ahead of you.
Is it too much to ask
for you to pump the brakes on this thing?
How about we do this…
Invite Murilo to the square one day,
so I can get to meet him.
Oh. I like that.
Mm.
Then we'll see.
[chuckling] Okay.
[cell phone ringing, vibrating]
INCOMING CALL
DAD
Answer your father, my love.
[cell phone continues ringing, vibrating]
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
I… It's just…
I don't have any more to say to him,
you know what I mean?
Tell you dad about Murilo.
Tell him about your life.
You haven't seen each other face to face
for nearly two years, give or take.
I know that.
It just feels like every time we do,
we end up fighting about something.
Anyway, why are you suddenly
sticking up for my dad?
Because he's still your dad.
My dad is dead.
[glass shatters]
What's the matter?
Nothing. Everything's fine.
["Remix Herói ou Vilão (Uma série Netflix
'Sintonia - Temporada 5'")
by MC Jottapê playing]
[birds chirping]
[song fades]
That was the first and last time
I put numbers before business, ND.
They almost cut off my hand, bro.
You can't underestimate
these guys, brother.
Yeah, but they're not going
for your hand anymore.
Now they're aiming for my head.
[tense music playing]
[cell phone chimes]
[ND] They're at my place.
We gotta do something, man.
These guys won't stop until we do.
[cell phone chiming]
You good, bro?
It's just my family, man.
Damn…
That's why I never got married, bro.
Nothing more messy than family, you know?
Putting down roots only slows you down.
Guys like the two of us
have way bigger responsibilities.
INSPECTION POINT
[police officer] Papers, please.
Glasses off.
INSPECTION AREA
[tense music continues]
All right. Good to go.
[sheep bleating]
[cowbell clanking]
-[helicopter blades whirring]
-[sirens wailing in distance]
[tires screeching]
[engine shuts off]
[intriguing music playing]
[man, in Serbian] We were too late.
The Brazilian's house was empty.
He could have left Serbia by now.
But he still has strong ties here,
in Brazil.
[menacing music playing]
[objects cluttering]
-[gasps]
-[music stops]
[tense music playing]
[breathing shakily]
Grandma!
Grandma! [whimpers]
Talk to me, please. Come on.
-Mom, come quick!
-[heart monitor beeping]
[somber music playing]
[Scheyla] Your grandma had a stroke.
We need to be strong, Bruna.
[game chiming]
I'm really gonna need your help.
At the house, at school…
-I'm not gonna… I'm not leaving her here.
-She's in better hands here, okay?
We'll take her home soon.
But it might take a while.
I can't believe you.
You give up without even trying.
Bruna, listen to me.
It's out of our control.
And you should really
call your dad tonight.
Why should I? What does…
does my dad have to do with any of this?
He was your age when his grandma got sick.
And she was the only family he's ever had.
You mean because he abandoned ours,
don't you?
Hey, Bruna, what did I tell you?
We have to stick together.
Me, you two, and your father.
I wish just once you would stop
making bullshit excuses for my dad.
I'm not gonna fight with you, Bruna.
Show some respect to your mother.
[cell phone ringing, vibrating]
Answer it.
Or are you going to send N.D. from V.A.
to voicemail?
[dramatic music playing]
[Scheyla] Bruna, come back here!
Enzo, come here.
Bruna! Bruna!
Bruna!
Hi, my love. How's everything going?
[Scheyla] My mother's in the hospital.
She had a stroke.
[ND] A stroke?
Are you okay?
And Bruna is missing.
What do you mean
Bruna is missing, Scheyla?
We were at the hospital.
We had a fight,
and Bruna bolted out of there.
You know her, she runs off, disappears.
She runs, but she always comes back.
How long ago was this?
This morning.
I've been calling, but she won't pick up.
I've called half the city,
nobody's seen her.
Are you saying
my daughter is out on the streets?
No one knows where she's at?
[Scheyla] Yes, your daughter!
Because she's just like you.
Stubborn as hell.
Calm down.
Let me think of something.
Well, while you think on it
on the other side of the world,
I'll be looking for her.
[phone line beeping]
[cell phone beeps]
[intriguing music playing]
[Moicano] Let's go to Italy.
You can ride it out there
until we figure out all this.
We killed two members
of Petar Ilic's family, bro.
They're gonna hunt us down like rats.
You go alone, man.
I gotta go to Brazil.
To Brazil?
You sure that's a good idea, bro?
You make everybody there think
you suddenly died,
so that you can disappear
without so much as a trace,
and now you're going back?
It's been four years, brother.
No one remembers me anymore.
-You stay here and take care of business.
-[sighs]
I need to take care of my family.
They're in danger because of me.
I'll call you when I get to Brazil.
We got this, bro.
You have my trust.
I got you, brother.
[in Serbian] Let's go to Italy.
-[engine starts]
-[car door closes]
[car approaching]
[engine stops]
[car door closes]
[breath trembling]
[in English] I don't know what else to do.
She could be anywhere right now.
Take a deep breath, Scheyla.
[Scheyla inhales]
A mother has one job.
And I failed.
I ask myself every day,
"Where'd I go wrong?"
[pensive music playing]
Look, my love, I've never been a mother.
But I know what kind of mother you are.
You haven't gone wrong.
She'll come back.
-Okay?
-[Scheyla sniffling]
Have faith. Everything will be okay.
[tense music playing]
Documents, please.
Come with me, please.
I have to open your bag, okay?
[customs agent 1] All clear?
[customs agent 2] All clear.
Welcome to Brazil, Mr. Lopes.
[music fades]
SÃO VICENTE HOSPITAL
[heart monitor beeping]
[breath trembling] Mom.
[pensive music playing]
I…
I try to be a good mother.
I've been remembering…
growing up,
how much worry and trouble
I must've caused.
[sniffles]
I'm so sorry, Mom.
[breath trembling, sniffles]
[door opens]
No one saw your sister at school today?
You're sure about that, Enzo?
I told you, Mom, no one's seen her.
Dad?
[ND] Hey buddy!
Oh my God! I missed you so much.
-Enzo…
-[ND] When did you get so big?
The present you made your dad at school,
go get it.
What's happening? What are you doing here?
Where's our daughter, Scheyla?
I have it under control.
She should be home by now.
What do you think I've been doing?
You're here to supervise?
[ND] Supervise? Really?
I can't just be concerned
about my family's safety now?
[Scheyla] Concerned?
You've been on the other side of the world
this whole time,
but now you're concerned
about your family's safety?
[tense music playing]
[ND] Where were you?
-You tell me right now where you've been.
-Calm down, Luiz Fernando.
I was at a friend's place.
What friend?
A boy.
I slept over by accident,
and I missed school.
[Scheyla] By accident. [scoffs]
Haven't heard of cell phones?
I called you, Bruna. You didn't answer.
Your mother called you. You didn't answer.
It died.
[ND] Your phone was dead?
Okay, you are never stepping foot
out of this house again
without telling your mom first.
Do you understand?
You came all the way here because of this?
I was worried.
[footsteps approaching]
[Enzo] This is for you, Dad.
[music fades]
Oh, wow!
It's beautiful.
[kiss]
-You made this at school?
-[Enzo] Uh-huh.
Miss Martins gave each of us
a piece of paper
and told us to draw
a self-portrait of our family.
That's awesome, buddy.
I missed you.
[Enzo] I missed you too.
You can sleep here.
[pensive music playing]
Hm.
You could have given us a heads-up.
To come to my own house?
Is there something going on
that I don't know about?
Is this not still my house?
I'll make sure not to bother you.
[cell phone vibrating]
[cell phone beeps]
[tense music playing]
If you don't want to bother us,
then while you're here, don't leave.
[pensive music playing]
[Joel over phone] Yo, ND,
I'm here with the guys.
Why don't you come by so we can talk
about this shit with the Serbians.
[suspenseful music playing]
-ND.
-[ND] Hey, brother.
[man 1] The rat raised the stakes
too high.
-Thought he had an ace up his sleeve.
-[men laughing]
[man 2] When the deal went south
and things turned,
we sent him straight to hell.
[all laughing]
[man 3] That's the game. Your play, sir.
If you fuck this up, it's over.
[man 2] I'll raise.
Hey boys. ND.
-Yo, ND.
-ND.
[ND] What's up, my brothers?
-[man 3] You want in on the next hand?
-No, no, man. I'm jet-lagged.
Oh, hey, ND,
if you were in Italy, then you'd be
in the same time zone as Serbia, right?
You're funny, brother.
Moicano's over there.
Plan's still going down. Our guy's on it.
So, ND.
It's just that right after you left,
we tried to track him,
but his phone went dark, bro.
And then we had someone send us this.
[dramatic music playing]
The SUV didn't make it to Italy.
This doesn't mean anything, man.
This is just another burnt car.
Moicano's alive.
He's just up to his bullshit, man.
I was the one that got him
into the business, in Paraná.
If he were up to his bullshit tricks,
I think I'd know, bro.
But my gut says he's not.
You know what? ND is a pretty lucky guy.
He was supposed to go on that car,
but instead he's here with his brothers.
Alive and well. Right, ND?
[man 1] Damn right.
I don't get you, man.
[tense music playing]
[Joel] Let's relax.
Hey, Betoneira.
How many years of jail you think
you and I got combined? Thousand?
-Something like that.
-[Joel laughs] Maybe more.
We're old men, on the run.
Let's relax
and not make assumptions, right?
Right, Joel.
[man 2] On a serious note, brothers.
Some of this organization's funds
appear to have gone missing.
We're all aware of that, right?
[tense music continues]
We'll have to take this upstairs.
That's right, brother.
Well, Nando's finally back in town.
He's with his family.
His wife, his kids, his brothers…
And now, Nando…
This is the best made in the world,
Japanese whiskey.
Those guys know how to make
the whiskey I like.
It's a worldwide sensation, man. Drink up.
-Arigato!
-[all] Arigato!
-[Betoneira] Look, Platina.
-[Platina] The luck of a cheat, huh?
I'm just lucky, my brother!
Good clean luck!
RECENT
MOICANO - MISSED CALL
[door opens]
-[ND] Good morning.
-Morning.
I was crunching some numbers before bed.
Counting the time I was in prison,
after you were arrested I mean,
we've spent more time apart than together.
Can you believe that?
Yeah, but we're raising
two children together, Scheyla.
No.
Raising children means being around.
Both of us.
You'll have to wake the kids. I'm leaving.
I'm going to the hospital to see my mom.
[keypad clicking]
[knocking on door]
[ND] Sweetheart!
[sighs]
[ND] Bruna!
Enter.
What's up?
Want some breakfast?
You choose it, I'll make it.
[sighs] What do we have to eat?
[sighs]
-[ND] Your brother still hasn't come down.
-[keypad clicking]
You have to wake him up.
He's a heavy sleeper.
Sweetheart, we need to talk.
Am I pissing you off already?
Bruna.
Do you have any idea
what your mom went through
when you ran away?
[keypad clicking]
Are you paying attention?
Yup.
So put down your phone already.
[cell phone clicks]
You spend your whole day on that thing.
And who's this boy
that you spent the night with?
I asked your mom. She doesn't know.
Why have we never heard of him before?
Grandma's heard of him.
Yeah, but your grandma isn't here.
How old is this boy?
Who's his family?
If you don't know my friends
or their parents,
that's not my problem. It's yours.
[ND exhales]
When I call you,
you never answer the phone.
It's been two years since I've seen you.
Because you didn't want to.
If you could've come back this whole time,
then why did you wait this long?
Watch your tone, girl.
All of a sudden you think
you run this house again?
[invigorating music playing]
I'm gonna eat in my room.
Bruna, come back here.
Bruna!
[sizzling]
Shit.
[cell phone chimes]
[Joel] Here's the deal, ND.
We're looking into this Moicano guy.
Don't worry, I'll keep you updated.
[man singing worship song]
[suspenseful music playing]
I can't believe it. Dude!
-[laughing] Is it really you?
-[ND laughing]
-[man] Dude, how you been?
-I've been good. And you?
I'm good. Happy to see you.
[boy chuckling]
[man] Look! Check it out. [laughs]
Your boy's all grown up now.
Congratulations.
Yeah, man.
His mom used to be his favorite,
but now it's me.
Maybe it's just this age.
Yeah, my boy was the same way.
Now I'm the father of a teenager
and it's a whole 'nother story.
The second you think you've got it right,
you screw something else up, man.
I can't imagine Chiquinho at that age.
But if my guy's like me,
he'll be chillin'.
You? Chillin'?
-[man laughs]
-[laughing] You're crazy!
Man, Chiquinho might be hyper,
but no one compares to you.
-You remember back in school?
-I remember.
When you and Rita got together.
Man, even I got in trouble.
You guys were a nightmare, man. [laughing]
Have you talked to Rita at all lately?
Not yet.
You know what Rita's like, right?
She likes to take her time, no small talk.
But I'll get in touch with her.
That's good.
-So you're back for real this time?
-Nah, man.
Just sorting out some issues at home.
And one of them's called Bruna.
Heard of it?
I have.
You know, man…
Guess who's getting ready
to perform on this stage?
Chiquinho?
The one and only. Bruna.
Seriously, man?
I asked her to perform at a service.
I've only seen her sing once.
I didn't even know that she…
That she liked it that much.
-Well, she does.
-That's cool.
We all have our ways
of expressing ourselves.
Once you understand hers,
I bet she'll listen to you.
[Bruna singing worship song]
[chuckles]
[tense music playing]
[man over phone] First of,
much love to you all, brothers.
I miss the days
when crime meant something.
You know, respect, loyalty,
a code you really lived by.
May God always be on our side.
So I hear there's been some problems
over there. Let's hear it, brothers.
I'll start
by filling you in on everything.
We're here today
because of some missing money
that resulted
in the death of two Serbians,
members of Petar Ilic's family.
And also because of the disappearance
of our brother who's been in Europe. Yeah?
Right, Joel.
That's right, my brothers.
Our comrade Moicano
is presumed to be dead.
We still haven't heard from him yet, true.
But if your godson shows up, Buda,
tell him that we want him to come in
for a debrief, please, okay?
I'm not sure how he'll make it,
if he's dead.
[ND] You think so, bro?
When me and Moicano were in Europe,
he was solid.
We would've taken a bullet for each other.
But when I went
to look up his record, man,
I dug up a ghost.
This is a picture of the rat
before plastic surgery.
Paulo Lopes,
who everyone here knows as Moicano,
doesn't exist.
But who does exist?
Gumercindo Queiroz. "Govinda."
Who was a part of the crew in Roraima.
[man over phone] You lost me, ND.
Explain more clearly, man.
[door opens]
Please, take a seat.
Tell them what you told us.
[woman] My name is Rosana.
The man you saw in the photo
is Gumercindo.
My husband.
But he suddenly went missing
a few years ago.
I thought he was dead
or in jail or something, but…
But a couple of years passed by,
and my cousin found out
he was living under another name.
Me and my daughter,
we went after him.
When he found out
the two of us were looking for him,
he went to Europe.
That's all I know.
I just want to move on with my life.
I have no idea
what he's been doing all these years.
My daughter and I
had nothing to do with this.
Please, please don't blame me.
You're just giving us some information.
Rest assured that nothing bad
is going to happen to you or your family.
You can go. Appreciate it.
Walk her out.
No.
I'll give it to him myself.
Goodbye.
Govinda was already a dead man in Roraima.
He'd stolen from one of our brothers.
That's what happened.
[man over phone] I remember.
When we went after that rat,
he disappeared.
[Buda] No, no. You have the wrong guy.
Moicano was baptized in Paraná with me.
Brother, Govinda faked his death
in Roraima, then turned around
and decided he'd be rebaptized
as Moicano in Paraná, man.
Don't you get it?
Are you trying to say
this organization is a failure?
That we're all idiots?
And that we can't keep track
of our own members?
Why are you putting words
in my mouth, brother?
Is that what I said?
Everyone here
has their own responsibilities.
Everyone here has their own jobs to do.
We're supposed to background check
everyone in this organization?
And this guy had a fake ID, brother.
He took advantage of a flawed system
and became someone else, right?
[man over phone] Got any proof of this?
Where're you getting these ideas from?
[sighs]
That's him, in Portugal.
Days after his car went up in flames.
Look at the scar on his hand, it's him.
Moicano stole our money
and blamed the Serbians.
And then he made a run for it.
Buda, explain it to your brothers.
How could you baptize a maniac like that?
Man, he seemed like a good dude.
He was responsible, never made a mistake.
[man over phone] That rat was thrown out
because he betrayed us.
He disappears
and comes back to fuck us over again?
That's why
these streets are a fucking mess.
Everybody stealing from each other,
killing each other.
And none of you have
your own brothers' backs anymore.
That rat may have gotten away
the first time.
Now he's getting
motherfucking exterminated.
Straight up.
[man over phone] That's right.
God may be the judge,
but we give the verdict.
Those traitors can go straight to hell.
Find him, brothers.
Buda, you're his godfather.
This is your responsibility.
Finish the job.
With all due respect, brothers.
I would like to make it clear
I'll be taking care of this one.
[man] If you're willing to put your neck
on the line, then the job's yours, man.
Whatever you have planned
for that fucking snake,
don't let it take too long.
Let this be an example.
And make it very painful. You got that?
Moicano's turning
into our bargaining chip with the Serbs.
Good!
[man over phone] The order's officially
been given, ND. We good?
[music fades]
-[school bell ringing]
-[indistinct chatter]
There's no way this is gonna work.
Stay calm.
-Yo, let's move! Let's move.
-Come on!
[both chuckling]
[Bruna] Careful!
If I get failed for ditching,
my mom'll kill me.
Especially with my grandma
in the hospital.
[boy] How is she?
She's better.
They finally took her off the ventilator,
but she's still in the ICU.
I know it might be a while.
But she'll be fine.
[Bruna] I planted those flowers with her
after we moved here.
Where'd you move here from?
Everywhere you could possibly think of.
I think I've moved more times
than probably anyone else in history.
But why?
Come on!
You know so much about me already.
You've even been to my place.
I told you my dad has another family.
But you won't tell me anything.
There you go.
-Now you know.
-[chuckles]
Tell me more.
You and the kids are gonna have to move.
Are you serious?
Nando, I love this house.
It's close to the kids' school
and my salon.
It's a safe neighborhood.
Scheyla, I have to get out of Serbia.
And I want this family somewhere safer.
You're kidding me. Always a sacrifice.
How about you compromise for once?
Why don't you just go alone again?
This is none of your business, Bruna.
-Please go to your room, Bruna.
-Or what?
You're gonna slap me again?
Why can't you be more understanding,
more like your little brother?
Cause maybe, unlike me,
my brother hasn't figured out
you'll be leaving again soon,
and you won't be back
for who knows how long.
[intercom ringing]
Hey, did someone order pizza?
[woman] We thought
you'd like the surprise.
-[Scheyla] Yes, somebody did order pizza.
-[man 1] What's up?
You look so handsome, Chiquinho.
-[man 2] How's it going, Scheyla?
-[Scheyla] Aww. How are you?
-[man 1] Boo-yah.
-[woman] Hi, my love.
[Scheyla] Can you take that, honey?
Guys, make yourselves at home.
Our house is your house.
-Damn, bro.
-[ND] Shit!
[man 2] Good to see you. How are you?
-[ND] How are you, man?
-Too long, dude.
-How you been?
-[ND] Doing good.
-You cleaned up a little, huh, bud?
-You noticed, huh?
Could almost pass for a businessman
with this fit.
You know it.
-And the bikes?
-No, it's in the past now.
-Now I just Uber everywhere, bro.
-End of an era.
I'll go help in the kitchen.
It's good to see you.
[ND] Rita.
-Hey.
-[chuckling] Hey.
-The three amigos together again, huh?
-[both] Yeah.
-I've missed you guys.
-So have we.
-Thanks, that's plenty.
-[Enzo] Press this one to make him jump…
Buddy, take Chiquinho
to play video games in your room, okay?
Let's go play upstairs, Chiquinho.
I was gonna tell you I was back.
I just needed some time
to try to get my head straight.
[Rita] I figured.
I'll get over it.
[sighs]
I missed my family like crazy.
Well, actually I missed you all.
Yeah, I know you and I might be going
through a rough patch right now,
but I must admit, I really did miss you.
[both laughing]
-You seem really good.
-Hmm.
[ND] It's nice to see you like this.
You deserve it.
Thank you, brother.
I feel happy.
-We have to make a toast, my friend.
-Okay.
[upbeat music playing]
Since the whole family's here tonight,
let's raise a glass to Laura.
[Scheyla] Thank God
she's getting better. [sighs]
-To Laura.
-[all] To Laura.
I thought you would love the pizza idea.
Remember the last time we did this?
At Rita's house, right?
How could I forget, right?
Chiquinho threw up all over me.
-Disgusting.
-Oh, no!
That was a crazy night.
Let's move on to something nicer.
Shall we talk about our star's big debut?
-[Scheyla] How do you feel?
-Just nervous.
Everyone has it
in their planners, right, guys?
Well, all but one.
[chuckling awkwardly]
You know, if it weren't for your dad,
I wouldn't be a singer, don't you?
-[Bruna] What do you mean?
-The first song I ever wrote was stolen.
And if it weren't for this guy here,
there'd be no MC Doni.
You used to be, like, MC Don…
-Dondoka.
-Dondoka. That's right.
[Bruna] Who's Dondoka?
At the time, she was the biggest MC, yeah?
-[Scheyla] Yeah, she was.
-[ND] She was huge.
You hear that, honey?
Your old man was once an MC's manager.
Pretty cool.
[Rita] An MC's manager…
How about the wrestling matches
at those shows?
[Scheyla] Oh my God.
I remember it like it was yesterday,
that beating you took from Jussara,
remember?
How could I let myself forget
something like that?
Your coworker, Jussara?
That's the one. My God, she was crazy.
Imagine, me against her.
Who do you think got the worst of it?
-You, right, Auntie?
-[Rita] Ding, ding, ding.
But no one could beat that woman though.
Wait, didn't she try
to kick your ass too, Formiga?
We were at a party,
and someone ended up breaking her cooler.
For some reason she thought I did it.
It wasn't enough
that she'd beaten up your aunt,
she wanted to beat up your uncle now.
Think I stood up to her?
She was nuts back then,
but she's better now, huh?
Well, kinda.
[Rita] Nah, I doubt it.
[all laughing]
[tense music playing]
[Joel] I told the Serbians
we wanted to meet
to straighten out this whole fuckin' mess.
[ND] That's perfect.
Let's hand over the rat and settle this.
[Joel] Ilic.
We're here as a sign of respect for you
and our longstanding partnership.
And to prove it.
Moicano.
He's the one who stole the money
that was missing from the deal.
[Joel] We're very sorry for your loss.
But that bastard's grave
is already dug for you.
And next month's shipment
is free of charge, okay?
I was born in Yugoslavia.
I fight in the Bosnian War.
I see many comrades die in battle.
I was tortured.
All of this, I can forget.
But the thing
I can never be able to forget,
your men have killed my family.
This I will carry with me forever.
Someone must pay for this.
But business is business.
And the money must keep moving.
[tense music builds]
-[gunshots]
-Shit, Joel. What the fuck?
-Watch out. Hide!
-[Joel] Hurry, ND. Come on, let's go!
[grunting]
[groans]
[ND] We're fucked, man.
There's more. There's more!
[tires screeching]
[grunts]
[exploding]
-[gunshots]
-[Joel] Now, N.D.
Let's get outta here!
[gunshots]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[ND] So it was you, Buda?
I knew you were a snake.
-You know you're gonna die, bro.
-[Buda groaning]
I'm gonna kill you,
and then I'm gonna kill your partner.
You're both going straight to hell, rat.
-[keypad clicking]
-[Buda groaning]
[cell phone ringing]
[ambient music playing]
Hey, Buda.
You get the job done already?
[ND over phone] Hi, Govinda.
Did you really believe
you would screw everybody over
and get away with it?
You dug your own grave.
[dramatic music playing]
[hip-hop music playing over speakers]
Stop.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
-Everything okay?
-Mm-hmm.
It's just that
I've never had a guy over to the house.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
-I'm special I guess, huh? [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
[music stops]
Your grandma?
I'll go visit her later tonight.
Your dad?
Wow, you look just like him here. Uh…
Sorry.
You get like this
every time we talk about him.
I guess I just wanted to know why.
Fuck, that's my bad.
Sorry, I shouldn't have…
Hey, if you wanna talk to me,
I wanna listen.
I understand.
-[exhales]
-Trust me.
Murilo…
Yeah?
You have to promise you won't tell.
Tell… Tell what?
Just promise this stays
between you and me, okay?
-But why do I need to promise…
-Please, Murilo.
Okay, okay. I promise.
[pensive music playing]
My dad is N.D. from V.A.
Who's that?
He was a drug dealer.
What?
Like, do you mean…
Like mob cartel shit? [chuckles]
[cell phone clicks]
[keypad clicks]
[man] One of the leaders of São Paulo's
most powerful criminal organization,
Luiz Fernando Silva,
also known as N.D. from V.A.,
was arrested last Friday
in downtown São Paulo…
Holy fucking shit.
I remember that. Fuck.
That… That's your old man?
Does that mean your dad's killed people?
-No, he's not a…
-Does your dad keep his guns here?
-No, of course he doesn't. I'm… I mean…
-This is insane!
-Like, oh my God. I'm, like, what…
-Look, Murilo, forget about it, okay?
-Just forget I said anything.
-Uh…
I think you should probably go,
and we can talk more about it later.
I'll text you. Please, just go.
-Okay. Sorry for being…
-Murilo, I said we'll talk about it later.
It's just a lot to take in.
Listen…
I'm not like my father. Okay?
I know.
Come here.
Relax, okay? I'm not gonna tell anyone.
-Come here.
-Look…
You should go.
We can talk about it another time, okay?
Okay.
See you tomorrow?
[door closes]
[Bruna] You were right, Grandma.
[sighs]
I should've given it more time,
like you told me to.
We all make mistakes, my dear.
They're a part of life.
What's important
is that you learned from it.
It shows that you are way more mature
than me or your mom were at your age.
[Grandma chuckles]
[door opens]
Be right back.
-I love you.
-I love you more.
[Grandma chuckles]
Laura…
I know I'm probably the last guy
you wanna see right now.
[breathing shakily]
[ND] But I came here to apologize.
I wanna thank you…
for being so wonderful
to your grandchildren.
You mean the world to them.
Thank you for taking care of my family.
[Grandma] When I first met you,
you were just a boy.
[chuckles]
I may not have given birth to you…
but God knows
how much I suffered over you.
He knows how I worried.
And He knows all the sleep I lost.
You took years off my life.
[chuckles, sighs]
Oh, my son…
You need to know…
You are powerful, son.
Your strength has always been
your greatest virtue.
I see a lot of that strength
in my grandchildren.
When are you finally going to slow down
and realize what really matters the most
in your life, my dear?
What will it take?
Your children turning their backs on you?
Enough.
Just look what you've done to this family.
My time is coming to an end very soon.
And I will no longer be here
to keep you in line.
And to tell you…
Forget the past.
The future is in your hands.
You must know that.
It's time to make a change.
[breathing heavily]
Prove us all wrong, son.
Hmm?
Do it for your children.
[ND] God bless you.
[Grandma] God bless you too.
Do you think Grandma is giving up?
[ND groans]
You've lost a lot of people, huh?
Yeah.
But it never seems to get easier.
Why?
Because I've hurt too many people
in this life, Bruna.
But I've always tried to do right
by the people I love the most.
Really?
Honey, I never knew my father.
I didn't have a mother.
No one asked me
what I wanted to do when I grew up.
That was my childhood.
This job was the only option I had
at the time
to give you,
your mom, your little brother…
to give you a better life than I ever had.
You're right. We've had
a much better life.
But honestly, in my opinion,
love means
being present for your children.
[upbeat music playing]
And also…
you look ridiculous in that black hat.
You think?
[Bruna] I know.
-Then how about I put on the glasses?
-[laughing] No. Don't do that.
-[knocking on door]
-[ND] Scheyla?
[music fades]
The kids are in bed.
[dreamy music playing]
I was wondering if you needed anything.
I was on my way to bed too.
I've missed this.
Sleeping in the bed?
I meant you.
[Scheyla sighs]
Nando,
if you leave me,
promise me
you won't ever come back.
[music ends]
CAETANO SOARES SCHOOL
BRUNA: NEED TO TALK TO U
MURILO: WHAT'S UP?
BRUNA: MEET ME IN THE HALLWAY
[cell phone vibrates]
[intriguing music playing]
[school bell ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
[inaudible]
[cell phones chiming]
[girl scoffs]
[keypad clicking]
WANNABE GANGSTA
SHE'LL SCAM U WITH THAT DIRTY MONEY
BRO YOU'RE CRAZY FOR THIS
[cell phones chiming]
[students murmuring]
[students laughing]
-What did you say? Who did you tell?
-Calm down. Calm down.
-My bad, it's just…
-[laughs]
So now everyone at school
knows about this?
I know.
I might've told Kiko.
You swore to me you wouldn't tell anybody.
-You broke your word after you promised.
-I know, Bruna. And I'm sorry.
No! Sorry doesn't begin to fix
the mess you've created.
-Wait, Bruna. Bruna.
-[cell phones chiming]
[exhales]
Fuck.
What are you looking at?
[upbeat music playing]
[whirring]
-Hey, how are you, my love?
-Hi Jussara, how are you?
Good, my love. Good.
Hey. Come here. Come here.
-What's all this? Glowing, are we now?
-It's nothing, Jussara.
Tell me, girl. Did you go out last night?
I bet you got your freak on, huh?
-Stop it!
-Scheyla, hey!
I just, you know…
For once, I'm not stressed out.
I know when you're lying.
I'd never judge you.
-I know that.
-Scheyla, for the love of God.
-Everything's fine.
-With all you've been going through…
You deserve it, my love.
With your mom, with Bruna.
There's a lot on your plate, Schey.
Things are getting better, okay?
You're beautiful.
You've got a rockin' bod,
you're a great mom,
successful businesswoman.
Babe, if I were your age,
I'd be hooking up with everyone.
Anytime, anywhere. Everyone and his uncle.
-You know why I can relax a little?
-Hm?
-Because I have a partner like you.
-[cell phone ringing]
Sorry, gimme a sec.
Okay. Wow, would ya look at that.
She's addicted to that thing.
God, I love her.
Hello?
Well, Scheyla. As you know,
we've been having some issues with Bruna.
Right?
But this time,
she's actually assaulted another student.
Unfortunately, we've run out of patience.
Well, I'm very sorry to tell you this.
But the school board has met.
And we think
it's in everyone’s best interest
that your daughter leaves this school.
I don't get it.
Scheyla, letting Bruna stay here
with everything
your family's going through
may be detrimental.
This includes Enzo, of course.
-Just tell me.
-We wouldn't want him being bullied.
Tell me what's actually going on.
You can be honest here.
I can handle it.
All right.
The man you made out
to be a villain, N.D. from V.A., is dead.
-Now I get it.
-Scheyla, it would be too difficult--
I'll be taking my kids out of this school.
But not because of this.
Because I want to!
Because you aren't doing anything…
-Calm down.
-…to protect them.
You're letting these morons
judge my children.
Scheyla, the parents
will keep on pressuring us.
It'll become unavoidable.
Because they're all perfect.
And I'm the only one who's ever messed up.
And just so we're clear,
none of those assholes on your board
know me or my life.
[dramatic music playing]
[Enzo] Mom, why do we have to leave early?
We'll talk about it at home.
Brunita, get in the car.
Okay.
You two, what are you lookin' at?
Fuck off.
So what happened?
[tires screeching]
[tense music playing]
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
[breathing shakily]
[music fades]
[reporter] A series of explosions
in Europe
has left two dead and one wounded
in what authorities are calling
a suspected criminal dispute.
The target,
businessman Gumercindo Queiroz,
known as "Moicano,"
has surrendered to authorities
at the Brazilian Embassy,
where he awaits transfer to Brazil
-…to assist federal authorities…
-Go to your room.
Nando, I think I was followed.
-What do you mean, Scheyla?
-Someone followed me.
-What'd they look like?
-I don't fucking know. They followed us.
I… I told someone about you.
[tense music playing]
But I made them swear they wouldn't tell.
What is going on here?
[Scheyla] Everyone at her school
knows who you are.
And a car just followed us, okay?
What the fuck have you done, Bruna?
I already apologized to Mom.
Sorry doesn't take back
the shit you told your friend.
What did you tell them I do, Bruna?
-Dad, I didn't wanna say anything.
-Oh, you didn't want to?
Now our whole family is in danger
because of you, Bruna.
You better go upstairs to your room,
right now, okay?
Go!
The fuck was that?
[door slams]
Listen, this isn't only her fault.
It's mine then?
I just want to protect my family, Scheyla.
If you want to have a family,
you have to understand
that you don't get to make the calls
on your own.
I already warned you.
If you're gonna be here, then be here.
Or leave and don't come back.
[invigorating music playing]
-[Joel] Hey, brother.
-What's up, ND?
-[man 1] What's good, bro?
-You good, man?
Hey, ND. Everything good?
ND, I've got our brother on the line.
He wants to have a word with you,
talk about a few things.
Whenever you're ready, my brother.
We've got him right here for you.
[man 2 over phone] Yo, ND.
The good news is,
you killed one rat, brother.
Bad news is, you let the other one live.
Now what? What if he talks?
[man 1] Here's the thing.
You’re not acting like someone
in your position oughta act, ND.
All you've done is waste our time,
and you haven't fixed anything.
[man 3] The order was given, was it not?
And now you've gone and left us
with all your mess.
[man 2] He's right, man.
Now we're all in danger.
What are we gonna do about this? Tell me.
I'll take care of it, man.
But the thing is, my brothers,
that piece of shit is flying in
as we speak
with his very own police escort.
So how do you expect to do it?
If we go down, I can promise you
I'm going down with you.
Don't worry, I'll smash that rat
with my own two hands, man.
[man 3] Now you're talking.
Catch that rat and make him pay.
Better get moving though,
because that bastard lands in two days.
You've made your point.
ND is our brother and my partner.
And speed is his specialty, my brothers.
[man 2] That's it, then.
ND'll take care of it.
Watch yourself, ND.
All the heat's on you now. You got that?
Understood, brother.
I've got this. I won't let you down.
-[man 1] You got this, ND.
-[man 2] Thanks, brother.
[tense music continues]
That asshole!
[cell phone vibrating]
Hi, Scheyla.
[Scheyla crying] Luiz Fernando, the…
My mom, she's not…
She didn't make it.
[somber music playing]
[crying]
Your grandma loved you so much.
[Scheyla] Thank you. [crying]
-[Rita] She's so proud of you.
-[Scheyla] Thank you.
She is, okay?
I'm glad you're here.
What difference
does my sitting in the car do?
When my wife is in there.
She just buried her mother,
and I can't be there for her.
My daughter's drifting
further and further away from me.
Everyone in my house is constantly
pointing out just how much harm I cause
when I'm around them.
[pensive music playing]
I don't know anymore.
I'm so tired, Rita.
Know what I think?
I think I know you too well,
Luiz Fernando.
I got to know N.D. from V.A.
and Nando,
whom I love.
My brother, my best friend.
But I also got to know
that sweet little kid,
the boy who quit school
to take care of his sick grandmother.
Who became a father too soon,
without even having a father of his own.
You know what all those versions of you
have in common?
Do you?
Unconditional love for your family.
That's why I believe in you, my brother.
I'm always on your side.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you even more.
[Bruna singing worship song]
It's really painful
to lose someone you love.
Grandma used to say that
when we decide to close
one chapter of a book
we begin a brand new one.
This is the only thing
I have left of my grandma.
She gave it to me
when I said I wanted to be a singer.
A singer?
[ND] Yeah.
A guy can dream, right?
But life had other plans for me.
The day that you were born…
[Bruna sniffles]
…was the happiest day of my life.
It was as if I'd finally found
the family I never had, in a way.
How long will you be sticking around
this time?
Dad, answer me.
Stop running away.
Please, just say something.
Is it important for you to have me here?
Very.
If I haven't told you before…
I really am sorry.
[tense music playing]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[ND] Lord Jesus…
I know I'm not worthy of your forgiveness.
I've lived in the darkness
for a long time.
[door opens]
[ND] Lord, I ask that you take my family
and my home beneath your wings.
Watch over those I love
and protect those who love me.
I know it's a lot to ask,
but pray that you forgive me
for what I am about to do.
I pray for the strength, for the courage
to do what needs to be done.
[engine whirring]
[indistinct announcement over PA]
[ND] May the blood shed today
be the last of its kind.
[keypad clicking]
[cell phone chimes, vibrates]
THE TARGET HAS LANDED
[intriguing music playing]
[ND] May those
who were unlucky enough to cross my path
be worthy of your grace.
[engine starts]
[wailing]
[ND] This hell ends today.
Amen.
[engine idling]
In position, waiting on the Feds.
[sirens approaching]
The rat's on the run.
Escort in position, let's roll.
[man over radio] Heads-up,
the cops are approaching the roadblock.
[ND] In sight.
[cop 1] Route blocked by construction,
traffic is stopped, over.
[cop 2 over radio] Copy, 15-01.
Stay on high alert.
[gunshot]
[man] Come on, ND, get 'em!
[cop 1] Command, we're under attack!
Get the fuck out!
Get the fuck out! Get out!
[man] Get on the ground! On the ground!
[Joel] ND, get down here.
Cops are on their way.
[groaning]
[cop 2 over radio] Unit two,
backup is on the way.
Unit two, confirm,
are there any casualties?
Requesting immediate confirmation.
[triumphant music playing]
[ND grunting] Get the fuck out,
you fucking rat.
You never had a family, huh?
You piece of shit.
[dramatic music playing]
[breathing heavily]
I was just playing the same game
you were, brother.
Only mine was better.
You put your family at risk
the whole time, didn't you?
You think my family was my weakness, man?
No.
My family's not my weakness.
They're my strength.
You know this won't be the last time.
For me, it will be.
[bullet casing clinking]
Ilic.
[Ilic] Now everything is settled
between us.
We can go on with business.
As usual, partner.
[cop 2 over radio] Command to unit two,
backup dispatched, units are on their way.
Backup is on its way.
[sirens approaching]
[singing worship song]
Say it out loud if you believe it!
[congregation applauds, cheers]
I would now like to invite Bruna
to join me up on stage,
who will be singing with us in praise
and pay tribute to her grandmother.
Let's make some noise for her, guys.
[congregation applauds]
Ready?
-[applauds fade]
-[soft music playing]
[Formiga] She's a star.
[Bruna singing worship song]
[inaudible]
Put your hands in the air, my friends!
Let us praise Him as one voice. Come on!
[inaudible]
-[song ends]
-[congregation applauding, cheering]
Well done! That's so good.
We love you, honey.
-What an incredible show, huh?
-I'm so proud of her.
-Of course you are. She's a mini Doni.
-You're right.
So this is officially farewell then?
[inhales] Yeah.
It's just that after losing my mom
and what happened with the school,
I'm just ready
to start over somewhere else.
What about Nando?
[intriguing music playing]
[man 1 over phone] Yo, my brothers.
We're here today to celebrate.
The rat's finally been exterminated.
What do you say, ND?
[ND] It's just sad.
It's sad that this had to happen,
that another one of our brothers
betrayed us.
And paid the price for it.
But let this serve as a reminder
that there's no place for greed
amongst us.
-[Joel] Absolutely.
-That's right, brother.
[man 1] I agree, ND.
It's not the first time
we've seen this happen.
There's only one rule, brother.
No matter how big you get,
you break your oath,
we make an example outta you.
Still, we got a problem.
Moicano's in the ground,
but he took all our money with him.
[man 1] That's true, brother.
The money Moicano stole from us
is what feeds our families, isn't it?
How we gonna make up for this loss, ND?
Don't worry, the money will be
in everyone's accounts tomorrow.
I'll cover the difference.
[man 1] Thank you, ND.
You've taken responsibility for this mess.
It's clear when someone comes along
who's built for this life.
And it's even more clear when someone
pours his blood, sweat, and tears
into this organization.
We've followed your journey here
over the years, ND.
From the beginning, you built up
this family with your loyalty and respect.
And it's time for your dedication
to be recognized, right?
It's time for you
to take on a bigger role.
We’re talking about real leadership here.
The coastal cities
are this business's lifeblood.
We're gonna send you to run things
in Santa Catarina.
How does that sound?
This is it, ND.
You'll be with your family, man.
You'll run the port of Itajaí.
You and the family'll live
on the beach, brother.
[Betoneira] Hell yeah.
You'll manage our finances. Off the radar.
Well? Are we agreed?
[Betoneira] Shake his hand.
I appreciate
everything you've done for me.
Because when we get
into this line of work,
it's to save ourselves
from the world out there, you know?
I've learned a lot over the years
in this business.
But it comes with a sacrifice, brothers.
My family's paid the price for it.
My wife went to prison because of me.
My kids are growing up without a father.
And despite all that,
my wife stuck right by my side.
But I still have two kids at home
who need me around, you know?
So, brothers, as of today,
I've decided I'm stepping back.
-The fuck is this?
-[Betoneira] What?
I'm officially leaving the game.
[Betoneira] You're fucking with us.
You forgotten your oath, ND?
[man 2] Once you read this, you pledge,
with one hundred percent certainty,
your loyalty to this brotherhood.
You know that's not how this works,
you can't just walk away.
Everything you have, everything you are,
is thanks to this organization.
Who do you think you are without us, huh?
[ND] This organization does not permit
dishonesty, collusion, envy, slander,
betrayal, cowardice, or corruption.
It is my vow to be instead a servant,
a voice for change, a warrior,
and a guardian,
in pursuit of the common good.
Because we are all for one
and one for all.
Freedom, justice, peace, courage, union.
[breathing heavily]
I don't know what to expect
from the world out there.
But if I'm given the chance to,
I will change.
-My kids will finally have a father.
-[sighs]
I need to put this life behind me.
[tense music playing]
[man 1 over phone] ND, I get it.
But if things are bad with us,
they'll be much worse without us.
No one forgets who you are.
Not the police, not the thugs.
N.D. from V.A. is a legend, man.
And legends don't die so easily.
There's no coming back after this.
You know you can never work
in this business again, right?
And that you're done
using this family's name.
So that's it. The order's given.
Starting today,
you, ND, are no longer part
of this organization.
Thank you
for everything you've done for us.
And for the loyalty
you've always shown us.
But make no mistake…
We have eyes everywhere.
You got that, brother?
Loud and clear, brother.
Guess that's it.
[phone line beeping]
Take care, bro.
-[Joel] Thanks, brother.
-[Betoneira] See you soon.
-[Joel] Catch you later, man.
-[man 3] Later.
-See you, brother.
-[man 4] Take it easy.
[music fades]
[Joel] Are you sure about this?
You're giving up your security,
business, money, respect.
Everything.
If I don't leave now, I never will, man.
You want me to give up my family?
[chuckles]
I wish I had your courage.
But watch your back, ND.
You and your family are easy targets now.
May God protect you.
[pensive music playing]
[music fades]
Hi, Dad.
[ND] Hi, buddy.
[game chiming]
Nando, this isn't the time.
I came here to talk to my family, Scheyla.
We're leaving in an hour, Luiz Fernando.
And I want to go with you.
[pensive music playing]
But what if you have to disappear again?
No, I'm not gonna abandon you this time.
I promise.
What about… What about me? Do I get a say?
Schey, I'm free.
I left.
Now it's just us.
I wanna be a part of this family for real.
Um, I don't… [sniffles]
I dunno, Dad.
I've never even lived with you.
[sniffles] But I've always been…
I always dreamed of having you here.
[Scheyla] If…
If everything you said…
If it's true,
that's what
I always wanted. [sniffles]
It's gonna be just us four
from now on, Scheyla.
Like it should've always been.
Love you so much.
I love you.
[intriguing music playing]
[game chiming]
[Scheyla] I don't think we have room
for all of Enzo's toys, do we?
What? Hey! [chuckles]
Honey, last box is ready!
[tense music playing]
Move. And put your hands
where I can see 'em.
-[ND] Okay, okay.
-Easy. One move and I'll end you.
What do you want?
You want cash? Take my money.
[man] Not everything's about money.
[ND] Who the fuck sent you here?
The hands of fate.
[ND] Just tell me, man. Who sent you here?
[Scheyla] Honey!
-Bruna, go get your dad.
-Okay.
I'm out of the game now man.
For real, I'm done with it.
I have a family, I have kids, you know?
-Oh, I know.
-[ND] Let's solve this another way.
[Bruna] Dad?
Go upstairs, now.
-[Bruna] Dad…
-Go upstairs right now!
[breathing heavily]
If you wanna get out of my house alive,
you better leave right now.
[panting]
Mom! Mom, Mom, Mom, Mom!
Stay with your brother.
[lock clicks]
[breathing shakily]
I know who you are, ND.
I know about Scheyla, Bruna, Enzo.
Drop the gun and back the fuck up now,
or I'll smoke your whole family.
Leave them out of this.
This is between you and me.
You can still walk away, man.
Just take the money
and get out of my house.
There's some things money can't fix.
Now. Drop the gun and give it to me.
Fucking do it.
Back up.
These streets never forget, ND.
Hey, at least you get to die
beside your family.
-[gunshot]
-[ND grunts]
[breathing shakily]
Scheyla.
-[breathing shakily]
-No. Don't look at him.
Look at me. Look at me.
Scheyla, look at me, please.
Look at me. Look at me. You're okay now.
[crying] You're bleeding.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Calm down. Relax.
-[Scheyla crying] Get me out of here.
-It's okay.
[crying] Get me out of here, Nando!
Get me out.
-Just breathe. Just breathe. [exhales]
-[Scheyla crying] Oh my God!
Just breathe.
Scheyla. Baby. Let's get the kids and go.
Let's go now.
[pensive music playing]
Calm down.
[Enzo] Mom.
[ND] I grew up thinking
life was a locked door.
And crime was the key.
But what I didn't know
is that some doors lock behind you.
I gained the world.
But I lost myself…
and my peace.
I learned to live with fear.
But I never learned to live
with seeing fear in the eyes
of the people I love the most.
Bad choices don't just hurt
the ones who make them.
They hurt those who carry your name.
I always said I did it for my family,
but I didn't.
I never asked them if they wanted this.
I have to live
with the mistakes I've made.
That's my punishment.
Where am I going?
I don't know.
I just ask for the chance
to be a better man from now on.
May God protect me
and more importantly,
may he protect this family.
["Remix Herói ou Vilão (Uma série Netflix
'Sintonia - Temporada 5'")
by MC Jottapê playing]
[song ends]
[pensive music playing]
[music ends]